双峰
第三季  第七集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     一只虾   吃冰棒
翻译     Silence   小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     没有影子   知之
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
杰瑞
Jerry?
-杰瑞  怎么了  -有人偷了我的车
- Jerry, what's going on? - Someone stole my car.
什么
What?
我没告诉你吗
Didn't I tell you?
杰瑞  怎么了
Jerry, what's going on?
有人偷了你的车吗
Someone stole your car?
你说的是同一件事吗
You say the same thing?
什么
What?
杰瑞
Jerry.
我觉得我嗑多药了
I think I'm high!
老天啊  杰瑞
Oh, good Lord, Jerry.
我不知道自己在哪里
I don't know where I am!
双峰镇警察局
这就是我找到的东西
This is what I found.
-是劳拉·帕尔默的吗  -是的
- From Laura Palmer? - Yeah.
"这是我昨晚的梦
"This came to me in a dream last night.
我叫安妮
My name is Annie.
我和戴尔和劳拉在一起
I've been with Dale and Laura.
好戴尔在小屋中
The good Dale is in the lodge,
他出不来
and he can't leave.
写在你的日记中"
Write it in your diary." Unquote.
这个"戴尔"就是指戴尔·库柏特工吗
"Dale" As in Special Agent Dale Cooper?
对
Right.
你觉得这是什么意思
What do you think this means?
不知道  但我肯定
I don't know, but I'm sure
这就是木头女士希望我找到的东西
this is what the Log Lady wanted me to find.
我觉得这个"安妮"就是安妮·布莱克本
I think that "Annie" is Annie Blackburn, a...
一个去过那里的女孩
a girl that went into that place.
你肯定这些是来自劳拉的日记吗
And these pages are for sure from Laura's diary?
是的  这些是她日记里面的
Yeah, these are from her diary,
那本在他朋友哈罗德·史密斯那里的日记
the diary found at her friend Harold Smith's.
这些就是之前被撕掉的四页日记的
These are three of the four pages that we saw
其中三页  之前一直不知去向
were torn out, missing.
还有一页没有找到
And there's... There's still one missing.
你觉得这些是怎么到这里来的
And how do you think they got here,
藏在我们的厕所门中
inside our bathroom stall door?
不知道  但你看看这个
I'm not sure, but look at this.
"现在是凌晨一点半
"It's 1:30 A.M.
我哭得很凶  几乎喘不过气来
I'm crying so hard, I can hardly breathe.
现在我知道那不是鲍勃
Now I know it isn't Bob.
我知道那是谁了"
I know who it is."
我很肯定是利兰把这几页藏起来了
I'm sure it was Leland who hid these pages.
他看到了这些日记  发现她已经知道了
He found 'em and realized that she knew.
我记得这个
Well, I remember this.
利兰·帕尔默  她父亲
Leland Palmer, her father.
你觉得他是什么时候把这些藏在这里的
When do you think he hid these?
不知道
I don't know.
利兰来过警局好几次
Leland came into the station several times.
就在那阵子
Once around that time,
我们把他带进来询问
we brought him in for the questioning
关于谋杀雅克·雷诺的凶手的事
of the murder of Jacques Renault.
也许他以为我们会给他搜身
Maybe he thought we were gonna frisk him,
所以他就把日记藏了起来
and that's when he hid 'em.
劳拉从没有见过库柏
Laura never met Cooper.
他是她死后才来的  对吗
He came here after she died, didn't he?
她说安妮是在梦中对她说了这些话的
She said that these words from Annie came to her in a dream.
她说的话...
This thing she said...
"好戴尔在小屋中
"The good Dale is in the lodge
他出不来"
and can't come out."
但是那晚哈里看见库柏
But Harry saw Cooper
和安妮一起从小屋出来了
come out of the lodge with Annie that night.
医生和哈里带他去了大北方酒店
Doc and Harry took him over to the Great Northern,
但如果好库柏在小屋里
but if the good Cooper is in the lodge
出不来
and can't come out,
那和安妮走出小屋的
then the one who came out of the lodge with Annie that night...
就不是好库柏
was not the good Cooper.
而且之后他很快就离开了镇里
And he left town soon after.
那天还有谁看见他了
Who else saw him that day?
我说了  还有海沃德医生
Well, like I said, Doc Hayward,
还有没有其他人我就不知道了
but I don't know who else.
那我们跟哈里讲一下最新情况
Let's bring Harry up to speed,
看看他怎么想
see what he thinks.
能让他接一下电话吗
Can you get him for me?
我很乐意等着
I'd be happy to wait.
哈里
Harry.
他们把你弄到哪去了
Where the hell they got ya?
不是吧
Oh, no kidding.
该死
Damn.
很遗憾  哈里
I'm sorry, Harry.
我就是想跟你谈谈几件事情
Uh, just wanted to talk to you about a few things.
对
Oh. Right.
我...  休息吧
W... Get some rest.
我一会儿再打来
I'll check in later.
不是  没什么要紧的事
No, nothing urgent.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
好好休息
Just get rest, and...
还有  哈里  帮我个忙
and, Harry, do me a favor.
战胜它
Beat this thing.
好了  哥哥
All right, brother.
再联系
Later.
-但这就是你的卡车  -我知道这是我的车
- But that's your truck. - I know it's my truck.
我不能在这里跟你谈这个
I can't talk to you about this here.
我告过你了  请走吧
I told you. Please go away.
但如果刚才不是你在开  我得知道是谁
But if you weren't driving, I need to know who was.
我会告诉你的  把事情原原本本地告诉你
I'll tell you. I'll tell you the whole story.
我们找个别的地方
I'll meet you somewhere,
但我不能在这里跟你谈这个
but I can't talk to you here.
求你了  你快带我离开这里
Please, you've got to get out of here now.
在斯帕克伍德21前的伐木路
The logging road above Sparkwood and 21.
靠近琼斯家吗
By Jones'?
过了琼斯家  小溪边上
Just past Jones', down by the creek.
是是  我知道了
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I know it.
那里见
See you there.
我两个小时后去那找你
Um, I-I'll meet you there in two hours.
那就是四点半
4:30, then.
请离开吧  马上离开
P-please leave. Please leave now.
杜鲁门警长
是你吗  医生
Is that you, Doc?
我是弗兰克·杜鲁门警长
This is Sheriff Frank Truman calling.
很高兴听到你的声音
Good to hear your voice.
哈里在哪
Where's Harry?
哈里这几天身体有些不适
Harry's, uh, a little under the weather these days.
是吗  祝他一切都好
Yeah? Well, give my best to him.
你知道网络电话是什么吗  医生
Uh, do you know what Skype is, Doc?
我一直都在用
I use it all the time.
有一天  我给穆勒太太看湿疹
Just the other day, I diagnosed Mrs. Mueller's eczema.
都不用离开自己的椅子
Never had to get out of my chair.
你的网络电话昵称是什么  医生
What's your Skype handle, Doc?
我也建一个
I'll, uh, saddle up.
米德伯理医生
MiddleburyDoc.
很快就来  医生
Be right with you, Doc.
好了
Now.
看到你了  医生
There you are, Doc.
什么事
What's this all about?
医生  你还记得很久之前
Doc, do you remember way back when,
哈里叫你去
the night Harry called you in
大北方酒店
to examine Special Agent Dale Cooper
检查戴尔· 库柏特工的身体
at the Great Northern?
我不记得今天早餐吃了什么
I can't remember what I had for breakfast this morning,
但我不会忘记那事
but I remember that.
告诉我你还记得些什么内容
Tell me what you remember.
我们都了解阿库
Well, we all knew Coop,
可是他那天表现得非常...
but that morning he was acting mighty...
奇怪
strange.
然后呢
And?
我带他去医院
I took him to the hospital,
他检查的时候我就在附近转转
and I had him checked out while I made my rounds.
大概一个小时之后
About an hour later,
我看到他穿着整齐
I saw him sneaking out of intensive care,
偷偷地从重症病房里溜出来
fully dressed.
他...他转身  然后
He... he turned, and...
然后他看到了我  接着
And he looked at me, and...
我又看到了他那副奇怪的表情
I saw that strange face again.
我大声叫他
I called out to him,
可是他没有理我
but he didn't say a word.
他转身就走了
He just turned around and walked out.
他在重症病房里做什么
What was he doing in intensive care?
我...我想了一下
I-I thought at the time
他可能顺路探望奥黛丽·霍恩
he might have been looking in on Audrey Horne.
银行发生那可怕的事
That terrible business at the bank, and...
她那时处于昏迷状态
She was in a coma.
身体怎么样  医生
How they biting back there, Doc?
有天早晨
You know, just the other morning,
我在睡衣里抓到了两天棕鳟
I caught two brown trout in my pajamas.
是吗
Yeah?
它们是怎样进到我睡衣里的
How they got in my pajamas,
我...我真不知道
I'll... I'll never know.
那你煮了它们当早餐吗
Did you make a breakfast out of them?
在河边用平底锅把它们煎了
Panfried 'em right out there by the river.
我还做了些炒鸡蛋
I had some scrambled eggs and...
还有一个英格兰松饼配越橘莓酱
and an English muffin with huckleberry jam.
不错
Yeah.
很高兴能跟你聊天  医生
Mighty good talking to you, Doc.
我会帮你向哈里问好的
I'll give your good wishes to Harry.
不论怎样
Whatever this is about,
我希望你能一切顺利
well, I hope it turns out all right for you.
继续您河边的工作吧  博士
Keep working the sunny side of the river, Doc.
再见  弗兰克
So long, Frank.
麦克利警探
Detective Macklay?
我是诺克斯中尉
I'm Lieutenant Knox.
你好  中尉
Oh, yes, Lieutenant.
很高兴见到你
It's good to meet you.
警探  感谢你的接见
Detective. Thanks for seeing me.
这不会花费太多时间
This shouldn't take long.
你前几天
You submitted a set of fingerprints
提交了一组指纹到我们的数据库
a few days ago to our database,
我们需要核实一下
and we need to verify the source.
我可以带你去看看
Well, I can show them to you,
我们的调查受到了阻碍
but our search was blocked.
希望能从你这里得到些头绪
That must have been from your end?
请带我去看看这些指纹
I'd like to see the prints, please.
你们从哪里收集到这组指纹的  犯罪现场吗
Where did you lift them from... A crime scene?
不是
No.
从一具尸体上收集的
Off the body.
还有尸体
There's a body?
是的  有一具尸体
There's a body, all right.
他的头去哪了
Where's the rest of him?
我们也不知道
We don't know.
这位先生多少岁
How old was this man?
快五十
Late 40s.
他是什么时候死的
When did this man die?
死了五六天吧
Within the last five or six days.
你们确定
You're sure this is the body
指纹是从这尸体上收集到的吗
you took those prints from?
没错
Yeah.
如果你喜欢的话  我可以再提取一次
I'm happy to pull 'em again for you, if you like.
如果知道了这是谁
It would sure help our investigation
对我们的调查肯定有很大的帮助
to know who this is.
先失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment.
长官  我是诺克斯中尉  长官
Sir. Lieutenant Knox, sir.
这次不单只是指纹
It's not just prints this time.
是一具尸体
It's a body.
戴维斯上校
是他
It's him.
你确定吗
You're sure?
指纹是从这具尸体上来的
The prints came off this body.
好的
Okay.
好了  我现在要打个电话
Okay. I have to make that other call.
还有一件事  长官
There's just one thing, sir.
什么事
What's that?
实际上  两件事才对
Actually, two things.
尸体的头不见了
The head is missing.
而且年龄也不对
And he's the wrong age.
你这是什么意思  辛迪
What do you mean, Cindy?
我的意思是
What I mean
他的头不在这里
is that his head is not here.
头不见了
It's missing,
还有那尸体显示
and the body
这是一名接近五十岁的男性
is that of a man in his late 40s
死亡时间是前几天
who died a few days ago.
如果他是最近死的
If he died recently,
布里格斯少校应该是七十多岁
Major Briggs should be in his 70s.
这中间肯定有什么不对
There must be some mistake.
我亲眼看过那具尸体
I've seen the body myself.
验尸官验证了年龄还有指纹
Coroner verified the age and the prints.
你先留在那里
Stay there.
我晚点再联系你
I'll get back to you.
我现在先打个电话
I'm making that other call now.
收到  长官
Yes, sir.
不允许其他人接近这尸体
No one else gets access to this body.
你介意跟我们说一下情况吗
You care to share any of this with us?
并不是由我来说...
You didn't hear it from me...
我想这案子
but I don't think this is going to be your investigation
很快就要交给上级调查
for too much longer.
谁
Yes?
请进
Come in.
事情办得怎么样了
How did it go?
不太顺利
Not well.
我说"你好  戴安"
I said, "Hello, Diane."
她回答说"要问库柏的事  对吗"
She said, "This is about Cooper, isn't it?"
我说"可能是"
I said, "Maybe."
她回答说  我只是复述她原话
She said, and I quote,
"他妈门都没有"
"No fucking way."
然后我就回家了
I was at home, dripping wet,
浑身湿透  十五分钟后差点就得肺炎了
on the verge of pneumonia 15 minutes later.
你那晚怎么样 警长
How was your evening, Chief?
这不是什么好消息啊  艾伯特
This is not good news, Albert.
她要见他
She needs to see him.
你出马吧
Your turn.
你会跟我一起吗
But you'll go with me?
-说"请"  -什么
- Say "Please." - What?
你听到的  别装了
You heard me.
请
Please.
联调局  你叫
FBI, champ.
戴安的朋友
Friends of Diane.
请进
Come on in.
谁来了
Who is it?
我的天
Oh, my God.
再见  戴安
See you later, Diane.
晚点见
Yeah, see you later.
这很快就可以结束了
Well, this won't take long.
我只是要把跟他说的话再和你们说一遍
I'm just gonna say the same thing to you I said to him.
别紧张  戴安
Now, take it easy, Diane,
我们坐下来
and let's just sit down
好好地聊一会
and have a nice, simple chat.
-你有咖啡吗  -没有
- You got any coffee? - No.
我也没有烟
I don't have any cigarettes either.
烟草的味道
Ah, the memory of tobacco.
可是我戒烟了
But I gave it up.
滚你的  戈登
Fuck you, Gordon.
她在对你人身攻击
Now you're getting the personal treatment.
你也想被人身攻击吗  你也滚吧  艾伯特
Oh, you want personal? Fuck you, too, Albert.
玩笑到此为止
Now that we got the pleasantries out of the way.
我从没和她谈到这个进度
I never even got this far.
戴安  你的前任老板
Diane, your former boss
前任特工戴尔·库柏
and former Special Agent Dale Cooper
被关在南达科他的联邦拘留所里
is in a federal lockup in South Dakota.
很好
Good.
戴安  你也许需要稍微改变一下态度
Diane, this may require a slight change of attitude on your part.
我的态度关你们屁事
My attitude is none of your fucking business.
不好对付啊
Tough cookie.
一向如此
Always was.
谢谢你  戴安
Thank you, Diane.
咖啡真好喝
Damn good coffee.
然后呢
So?
说吧  你们来这干什么
Say what you came here to say.
我们有预感出事了
We have a feeling something is wrong.
不知道具体是什么事
We don't know exactly what it is,
但是我们需要一个非常了解他的人
but we need someone else who knows him extremely well
去找他谈谈
to have a talk with him
然后告诉我们他的想法
and afterwards tell us what you think.
这事非常重要  戴安
This is extremely important, Diane,
这当中涉及到你知道的事
and it involves something that you know about,
这点就足够了
and that's enough said about that.
联邦监狱
Federal prison...
南达科他
South Dakota.
别挑刺  丑话说在前
Judge not, lest to be judged.
事实是
Listen, just the fact
你的行动比言语更有说服力
that you're here speaks louder than words.
滚你的  艾伯特
Fuck you, Albert.
你们看看这个
Look at this.
这边是二十五年前的库柏
Cooper 25 years ago...
另一边库柏两天前在监狱里
Cooper in prison two days ago.
完全一样  对吧
Identical, right?
也许吧
Maybe.
你们怎么认为
What do you see?
这个标记的位置是错的
This code mark's on the wrong side.
你觉得这说明了什么
What does that tell you?
监狱里的某个克罗马努人
That some Cro-Magnon at the prison
想要把这个上移  令其看似未经改动过
tried to line this up to make it look like the original,
但是他必须反向打印才行
but he had to reverse the print to do it.
"常非"  反过来写
YREV, the backwards word.
什么意思
What does this all mean?
塔米  你一直做得很好
Tammy, you've been doing excellent work,
通过了一个又一个的测验
passing one test after another.
伸出双手
Put out your hands.
掌心朝下
Flip 'em over.
我非常非常高兴
"I'm very, very happy
再次见到你
to see you again,
老朋友
old friend."
这是心灵之丘  心灵之指
This is the spiritual mound, the spiritual finger.
好好想想这些  塔米
You think about that, Tammy.
这是我们唯一的一张
That's the only known photograph we have of Cooper
库柏过去二十五年的照片
in the last 25 years.
里约郊外
That's outside of Rio...
他的房子
His house.
但在我们去搜查的时候
By the time we checked it out,
那房子却归某个伊帕内玛姑娘所有
it belonged to some girl from Ipanema.
他好像是我们在监狱里见到的那个人
Looks like the man we met in prison.
我们在监狱里见到的那个人
The man we met in prison.
苏城扬克顿联邦监狱
十分钟
Ten minutes.
我单独和他谈
And I speak to him alone.
最多十分钟
Ten minutes, tops,
或者我说结束就立刻结束
or it's over when I say it's over.
就是这样  戴安
That's exactly the way it's gonna be, Diane.
帘子和麦克风由你来控制
You'll control the curtain and the microphone.
我们非常地感谢你
And we're very appreciative.
再说一次你叫什么名字来着
What'd you say your name was, again?
塔米
Tammy.
滚你的  塔米
Fuck you, Tammy.
我就知道会是你
I knew it was going to be you.
很高兴再见到你  戴安
It's good to see you again, Diane.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
那是什么时候  库柏
When was that, Cooper?
我们上次见面是什么时候
When did we see each other last?
你在生我气吗  戴安
Are you upset with me, Diane?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得你在生我的气
I think you're upset with me.
我们上次见面是什么时候  库柏
When was the last time we saw each other, Cooper?
在你家
At your house.
对
That's right.
你还记得那晚吗
Do you remember that night?
我一直记得那晚
I'll always remember that night.
我也是
Same for me.
我永远也不会忘记
I'll never forget it.
你是谁
Who are you?
我不知道你什么意思  戴安
I don't know what you mean, Diane.
看着我
Look at me.
谢谢你  墨菲监狱长
Thank you, Warden Murphy.
-就这样吗  -是的
- That's it? - Looks like it.
再我们通知你之前  别放他走
Hold this man till you hear from us.
戴安
Diane?
听我说
Listen to me.
他不是我所认识的戴尔· 库柏
That is not the Dale Cooper that I knew.
请告诉你这话是什么意思
Please tell me exactly what you mean.
不是因为时间的流逝
It isn't time passing...
或他改变的方式
or how he's changed...
更不是他的样貌
or the way he looks.
而是这里
It's something here.
他这里绝对有些问题
There's something that definitely isn't here.
这样可以了  戴安
That's good enough for me, Diane.
可以了
That's good enough for me.
你在里面提到的昨晚
That last night you mentioned in there...
有什么我需要知道的吗
Something I need to know about?
改天我们再聊
You and I'll have a talk sometime.
我们会好好聊聊的
You and I will have a talk.
好吗
Okay?
好
Okay.
干杯
Cheers.
敬联调局
To the FBI.
听我说句话
Listen to me a minute.
告诉墨菲监狱长我有话要和他说
Tell Warden Murphy I have a message for him.
我要在他办公室里和他谈
I need to speak with him in his office.
想得美
Yeah, right.
就告诉他
Just tell him
我们要聊聊草莓
we need to speak about a strawberry.
让他坐下  然后你们出去吧
Sit him down and leave.
我已经把监视器关掉了
I've turned off the security cameras.
我们可以畅所欲言
We can speak freely...
私下聊聊
and privately.
狗腿
The dog leg.
那只狗有四条腿
That dog had four legs.
一条就是你在我车里找到的
One you found in my trunk.
另外三条和你正想得到的信息
The other three went out with the information
在一起
you're thinking about right now.
如果我出了什么事  会有两个
Two people you don't want coming around here
你不想看到的人来找你
if anything bad happens to me.
我怎么知道你知道...
How do I know you know anything about...
这些
this?
乔·麦克劳斯基
Joe McCluskey.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我要一辆车
I want a car.
便宜的租车就行
Cheap rental, if you like.
给我和雷·门罗用
For myself and Ray Monroe.
给车的柜子里备好东西
I want a friend in the glove compartment...
今晚一点
One A.M. Tonight.
稳健安全
Smooth and safe.
如果你想耍主意
And if your mind should wander to a place
让我没法活着出去
where I might not make it out of here alive,
记住狗腿
remember the dog legs.
我对你不感兴趣
I'm not interested in you.
你不会再看到我
You'll never see me again,
没人会再听到关于
and no one will ever hear anything more
乔·麦克劳斯基的事
about Joe McCluskey
或者你那位已死的草莓先生
or your late Mr. Strawberry.
你为什么不和我讲话  道吉
Is there a reason you're not talking to me, Dougie?
你和布什内尔之前在说什么
What were you and Bushnell discussing earlier?
我看到你...
I saw you...
拿着一叠文件进了他的办公室
walk into his office carrying a bunch of files.
有几位警官来找你  道吉
Uh, some police officers are here to see you, Dougie.
警官
Police.
让我想到我得打个电话
That reminds me of that call I have to make.
警官
Police.
要他们进来吗
You want them to come in here?
好吧
Okay.
琼斯先生
Mr. Jones?
我是弗斯科警探
Detectives Fusco.
警徽
Badge.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
你是谁  女士
Who are you, ma'am?
我是他的妻子
I'm his wife.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
我们是因为他的车而来
We're here about his car.
所以我才来
That's why I'm here.
你这话是什么意思
What do you mean by that?
我是来接他的
I'm picking him up.
他不知道他的车在哪里
He doesn't know where his car is.
被偷了吗
Was it stolen?
道吉  你的车被偷了吗
Dougie, was your car stolen?
偷
Stolen.
你报失了吗  先生
Did you report it stolen, sir?
先生
Sir.
你上报自己丢车了吗
Did you report your car as a stolen vehicle?
不  他没有报失
No, he did not report it stolen.
不然我肯定知道
I would know.
他的车不见了  我们也没见过
His car went missing. We haven't seen it.
这不是你们的工作吗
Isn't that your department?
没错  等报失之后
Yes, it is, once it's reported as missing.
我想现在亡羊补牢不算迟
Well, I guess this is as good a time as any.
他不知道车在哪里
He doesn't know where the car is.
他好几天没见过了
He hasn't seen it in a few days,
没错  很有可能
so, yes, there's a very strong possibility
被偷了
that it was stolen.
偷
Stolen.
那好吧  琼斯先生
All right, then, Mr. Jones,
你最后一次见到你的车是在哪里
where did you last leave your car?
我们要是知道
Well, if we knew that,
就知道该去哪里找了  是吗
we'd know where to find it, wouldn't we?
能形容一下你的车吗
Okay, can you describe your vehicle, please?
那是一辆破车  老是送去修
Ah, it's a terrible car, always in the shop...
银色四门廉价福特车
Silver, four-door, cheap Ford,
那个经销商都把它叫做
the kind they call down at that dealer
二手车
a "Previously owned" Car.
车是什么时候丢的
When, uh, did the car go missing?
道吉
Dougie?
Dougie.
几天前
A few days ago.
几...
Few...
天前
days ago.
你不报失有什么原因吗
Is there a reason why you didn't report your car missing?
原因  我告诉你原因
Reason? Yeah, I'll tell you a reason.
生活中有比车更重要的东西
There's more to life than cars.
太多车  太多事
Too many cars, too much going on,
道吉最近压力很大
and Dougie's been under a lot of stress lately,
如果你想知道真相  我也想
and if you want to know the truth, so have I.
警官们  你们找到车了吗
Officers, have you found the car?
你是谁  先生
Who are you, sir?
这地方是他的
He owns this place.
布什内尔·穆林斯
Bushnell Mullins.
道吉为我工作
Dougie works for me.
你们没找到他的车  对吗
You did find his car, didn't you?
车被找到了
The car has been found.
和一起爆炸案有关
It was involved in an apparent explosion.
多人死亡
Multiple fatalities.
你们为什么不一开始就告诉我们
Why didn't you tell us that to begin with?
死的人似乎和一系列
The deceased individuals had ties to a gang
汽车盗窃案有关
associated with multiple car thefts.
你们要的回答已经给你们了
Well, there's your answer.
不介意的话
Now, if you don't mind,
我们的儿子还在家里等着吃晚饭
our son's home alone waiting for his supper,
以防你们觉得我监护不当  顺便说一声
and in case you think we're neglecting him,
邻居在帮忙照看他
he's being watched by our neighbor as a favor,
我们要走了
and we'd like to go.
经过了非常漫长紧张的一天后
We were supposed to be home by now
我们现在应该在家里
at the end of a very long and stressful day,
我待会告诉你发生了什么  道吉
which I'll tell you about later, Dougie.
-我们走  -等等
- Come on, let's go. - Hold on.
我知道我们来这里
And I'm sure our being here
给你添了不少麻烦  女士
hasn't made your day any easier, ma'am,
但我们想让你们填一些文件
but we're gonna need you to fill out some paperwork.
如果你们不方便  我们可以代劳
Which we can take care of at your convenience.
明早给我们打个电话
Please, give us a call in the morning.
谢谢你们的合作
And, uh, thank you for your cooperation.
祝你们今晚愉快
Have a pleasant evening.
晚安
Evening.
他收保险的时候
I guess he won't have any trouble
肯定"完全没问题"吧
collecting the insurance, huh?
我对你给我的那些文件
I have some questions about those files
有点问题  道吉
you covered for me, Dougie.
但你去吧
But you go ahead.
那些可以明天再说
We can take care of that tomorrow.
谢谢  穆林斯先生
Thanks, Mr. Mullins.
谢谢...穆林斯
Thank you... Mullins.
我见过他们了
So I met with them.
我告诉他们该还多少就还多少
I told them what the arrangements were gonna be,
我还多给了他们不少
and I gave them more than they deserved,
他们不会来找我们了  好吗
and that's the end of them, okay?
关于车的事
Now, with this car business,
没错  肯定要找保险赔点钱
yes, there's gonna be some insurance money.
我也不清楚  但是道吉  好好想想
I don't know how much, but, Dougie, just think.
要是你当初没有把钱都赌没了
If you hadn't blown that money gambling...
两万五加保险的钱
$25,000 plus the insurance...
我们可以给你买辆新车
We could have gotten you a great new car.
现在谁知道我们还有什么
Now who knows what we'll get?
但是我不想再放你
But I do not want you running off
用那些奖金去赌博了
and gambling any more of that jackpot.
那笔钱是给桑尼·吉姆和我们的未来准备的
That money is for Sonny Jim and our future.
现在有这笔钱
Just 'cause you have it now
你也不能就这么失踪
doesn't mean you can just run off
拿我们的钱去冒险
and risk one more penny.
听到了吗
Do you hear me?
不许再去...
No more gam...
放开他
Get off him!
把他的手捏下来
Squeeze his hand off.
道吉
Dougie!
你们没事吧
Are you guys okay?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
道吉
Oh, Dougie.
怎么...你没事吧
What... Are you okay?
他就这么...就...
And he just... he just...
道吉走上前
Dougie took right over,
掐住他的喉咙
and he just chopped him right in the throat
说"放手"  我踢他
and said, "You get off," And I kicked him,
我打他  就是这样
and I punched him, and that was it,
然后...然后道吉就把他解决了
and... and Dougie just took care of business.
对吗  宝贝
Right, baby?
真是...太可怕了
It was... it was terrible.
拿枪的那个人吗
What about the man with the gun?
他冲向我
He ran right at me.
几乎把我撞倒
Almost knocked me down.
他闻上去好奇怪
He smelled funny.
受害者
Victim? Oh, no.
那家伙才不像个受害者
That guy didn't act like any victim.
道格拉斯·琼斯  他跟眼镜蛇一样敏捷
Douglas Jones... He moved like a cobra.
我就看到人影一闪
All I saw was a blur.
你第一次听到这些声音是什么时候
When did you first start hearing this?
上周吧
Sometime last week.
但我觉得现在更响了
But I think it's louder now.
也许是因为这里没有人
Maybe that's 'cause nobody's here.
别动
Don't move.
仔细听
Just listen carefully.
你觉得是从
Where do you think...
哪里来的
it's coming from?
现在听上去
Now... now it sounds like
像是从那里来的  对吗
it's coming from over there, no?
没错
It sure does.
不
No.
也不是这里
No, it's not here either.
这东西可能有点意思
Oh, this might be of interest.
今天寄过来的
It came in the mail today.
天啊
Wow. My God.
这可有点年头了
That's an old one.
我们20年前就用房卡了
We switched to cards over 20 years ago.
315房间
Room 315.
等等
Wait a minute.
我觉得库伯特工
I think that was the room
就是在那里中枪的
where Agent Cooper was shot.
库伯特工是谁
Who's Agent Cooper?
联调局的
FBI.
他应该  25年前来过这里
He was here, I don't know, maybe 25 years ago...
调查劳拉·帕尔默的死
investigating the murder of Laura Palmer.
劳拉·帕尔默是谁
Who's Laura Palmer?
亲爱的
Oh, that, my dear...
那可说来话长了
is a long story.
找维修工
Have maintenance, uh,
明天早上来看看这声音是哪里来的
check out that hum in the morning.
现在他们肯定已经下班了
It's getting way past quitting time.
谢谢你  霍恩先生
Thank you, Mr. Horne.
叫我本
Ben.
晚安  本
Good night, Ben.
贝弗莉
Beverly.
不好意思我迟到了
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
他怎么样
How is he?
今天过得不怎么样
We had kind of a rough day.
他好多了
He's better,
但我得给他加大止痛药量
but I had to give him extra pain medication.
好  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
他吃过东西了吗
Oh, has he eaten yet?
他在等
He was waiting.
-晚饭在炉子上  -好
- Dinner is on the stove. - Okay.
他在等你
He's missing you.
明天见  玛姬
I'll see you tomorrow, Marge.
对不起我迟到了  亲爱的
Sorry I'm late, honey.
你饿吗
Are you hungry?
我听到你开过来
I heard you drive up.
你为什么迟到了
Why were you late?
我有点事
I had some things to do.
要吃晚饭吗
Would you like your dinner?
什么事
What things?
我工作上有点事
I had some work to do.
出了点事  我得先做好
Some things came up, and I needed to do them.
你饿吗
Are you hungry?
不是很饿
Not really.
听我说  汤姆
Listen to me, Tom.
我知道你很痛苦
I know you're sick and suffering.
我知道
I know it.
但不要利用这点折磨我
But do not use that to fuck with me.
不要折磨我
Do not fuck with me!
我也不想回去工作
I didn't want to go back to work.
你知道我能有这份工作帮我们谋生
Do you know how goddamn lucky I am to have this job
有多走运吗
to help us survive?
我的天啊  别再闹了  汤姆
Oh, for crying out loud, do not fuck this up, Tom!
枪炮酒吧
是的  酒馆
Yeah, Roadhouse.
让·米歇尔
Jean Michel.
他当然喜欢  谁会不喜欢
Yeah, of course he loved it. Who wouldn't?
什么
What?
两个
Two.
我找了两个人去  他得付两个人的钱
I sent him two. He owes me for two.
什么  我不知道他们的名字
What? I don't know their names.
他想要金发妞  我就派了两个金发妞去
Uh, he wanted blondes. I sent him two blondes.
什么  操  我...多大
What? Fuck, I... How old?
她们有身份证  她们
They had IDs. They both had good IDs.
这和我们酒馆没关系
Look, this has nothing to do with the Roadhouse.
雷诺家已经
Roadhouse has been owned
经营酒馆57年了
by the Renault family for... For 57 years.
我们不会因为几个...
We're not gonna lose it now because of a...
15岁的好学生丢了这块地
A couple of 15-year-old straight-A students.
不  不
No, no.
这些女孩  她们是
those girls, they are...
妓女  简单干净
Whores, pure and simple.
据我所知  她们是好妓女
Ah, from what I hear, though, they were straight-A whores.
他得付我两个人的钱
He owes me for two.
米色的是租的
It's the beige rental.
这是你的电话
Here's your phone.
钥匙在车里
Keys are in the car.
你开车
You drive.
有人看到宾吗
Has anybody seen Bing?
没有  没有
Nope. No.